(Amy:)Hi. You're on
Fun with Flags.
KRIPKE:
Hey, I think I got cut off.
(Amy:)Hello, Kripke.
I have a flag question.
(Barry:)How many men
did you have sex with?
(Leonard:)Let's see. What's
young and fun?
(Leonard:)Uh, we could
go dancing.
(Leonard:)Are you actually
gonna dance?
(Howard:)Of course.
Yeah.
(Penny:)No one wants to see that.
(Penny:)Hey, how about skinny dipping
at the beach?
(Leonard:)No, I don't need
any fish nibbling my business.
(Penny:)Oh, there's a screening
of Moulin Rouge!
(Penny:)I heard the crowd
sings along and stuff.
(Leonard:)That sounds fun.
When's it start?
(Penny:)Midnight.
(Leonard:)Midnight. Really?
(Leonard:)You know what? Let's do it.
Okay, great!
(Penny:)Oh, wait. Uh, it's sold out.
(Leonard:)Oh, thank God.
Yes!
(Howard:)It says, rabies
in rabbits is
(Howard:)highly unlikely.
(Bernadette:)Oh, terrific.
It's not terrific.
(Howard:)Lots of highly unlikely things
happen.